And now we're going to make a, it's called a, it's a free form teapot.
Which means I'm just going to throw it.
I'm going to assemble it.
I'm going to move it around.
I'm going to make it to where this teapot looks like it's dancing, or I'm going to try.
So it's going to look like it's dancing or it's going to look like it's drunk.
Either one, it'll be good.
And they're fun to make.
It's all about assembling.
And, throwing these pieces, throwing slabs, all of it, it's real fun.
So you want to start with a nice wedged piece of clay.
And you want to remember once you get that wedged that that's the part that's going on the wheel head.
And that's the part with the dimple that's going to go up.
So other wise, this little dimple will give you problems all the way up.
Now we got that, want to bring it to the wheel.
Going to clean off our wheel head.
From there.
Alright.
Now I'm going to put that over there.
I'm going to save it.
Get this on center as much as possible.
Alright.
Now we're ready to go.